Guide to the Bert N. Corona Papers, 1923-1984
Department of Special Collections
- Newspapers, 1970-1983, Series 14
  - El Pregonero, published by the Centro Catolico Hispano, Al Servicio del Area Metropolitana de Washington, 2 issues, [broken series], Jan./Feb. 1980- Aug./Sep. 1980 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Prensa Estudiantil, published by MEChA at the California State University at Los Angeles, 4 issues, [broken series], Nov. 1975- Nov./Dec. 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - La Prensa San Diego, published in San Diego, CA, 4 issues, [broken series], Jan. 31, 1977-Nov. 30, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Proletario, published Por la Creación de una Fuerza de Oposición y Alternativa al Sistema in Chihuahua, Mexico, 1 issue, Mar. 15, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Pueblo, published in San Juan, PR, 2 issues, [broken series], Nov./Dec. 1978- Dec. 1979 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - El Quetzal, published in Orange County, CA, 3 issues, [broken series], May 1977-Aug. 1977 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - La Raza, published in Chicago, IL, 1 issue, Nov. 10, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - La Razon Mestiza II, published in San Francisco, CA by the Concilio Mujeres, 1 issue, Summer, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate Illustrated, published by the San Fernando Valley Board of Realtors, 1 issue, Jul. 11, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - The Register, published in Southern California, 1 issue, Sept. 8, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - El Renacimiento, published in Lansing, MI, 1 issue, Apr. 25, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - The San Diego Union, 1 issue, Feb. 10, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Santa Barbara News and Review, 1 issue, Jul. 19, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Scope, Reporting grass roots activities which promote the Community Education Services Program of the Children's Television Workshop, 1 issue, Apr. 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Semanario Azteca, published in Southern California, 2 issues, Aug. 10, 1983-Aug. 17, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Seniors on Parade, published by the Los Angeles City Federation of Senior Citizen Clubs, 1 issue, Jan. 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Service Union Reporter, published by the State Council of the Service Employees International Union, 1 issue, Jan. 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Sí Se Puede, published in Santa Barbara, CA, 2 issues, [broken series]; the flip side of the second issue is Common Ground, published at the University of California at Santa Barbara, Apr. 4, 1976- Feb. 6, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Sin Fronteras, Vocero del Trabajador Mexicano, published in Los Angeles, CA, 14 issues, [broken series], Feb. 1974-Mar. 1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - El Sonorense, published in Hermosillo, Sonora, Mexico, 1 issue, Dec. 14, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Southern California Teamster, published by the Council of Teamsters No. 42, 4 issues, [broken series], Nov. 3, 1976-Nov. 29, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Southern California Workers News, 1 issue, Jun. 1974 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - The Southern Patriot, published by the Southern Conference Educational Fund in Louisville, KY, 1 issue, Sept. 1973 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - The [San Fernando Valley] Sun and Breeze, 3 issues, [broken series], Jan. 26, 1977-Aug. 9, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Sun Valley Scene, Sun Valley, CA, 3 issues, [broken series], Jun. 5, 1980-Jul. 10, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - El Tiempo Chicano, published in National City, CA, 1 issue, Apr. 1979 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - El Trabajador De Canería, published by the Cannery Workers Committee in Sacramento, CA, 1 issue, Oct. 1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - The Trumpet Call, published by Christian Evangelical Churches of America in Oakland, CA, 1 issue, no date (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - UCSB in View, published by the University of California at Santa Barbara, 1 issue, May 4, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - UMAS Publications, 1 issue, Dec. 1970 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - El Universal, published in Mexico, 1 issue, Jun. 1978 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Universitario, published by La Universidad Autonoma de Sinaloa in Mexico, 2 issues, [broken series], Feb. 10, 1979-Aug. 23, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - University Times, published by the California State University at Los Angeles, 15 issues, [broken series], Apr. 30, 1975-Aug. 22, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - unomasuno, published in Mexico, 2 issues, [broken series], Jan. 17, 1978- Jan. 21, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Valley News, published in the Los Angeles area, 1 issue, Sept. 8, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - El Visitante, published by La Sociedad Interamericana de Prensa y La Asociación Nacional de Prensa Católica, 5 issues, [broken series], Mar. 12, 1978-Nov. 1, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Vital Signs, published by the Health Policy Advisory Center in San Francisco, 1 issue, May 1976 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Voice, Local 660 of the Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO in Los Angeles, CA, 1 issue, May 15, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - La Voz de la Escuela, published by Escuela de la Raza Unida, an alternative school in Blythe, CA, 3 issues, [broken series], May 28, 1975- Feb. 25, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - La Voz de México, published by the Comité Central del Partido Comunista Mexicano in Mexico, 5 issues, [broken series], Nov. 15, 1973-Apr. 1, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Voz del Pueblo, Spanish supplement to World Magazine, published in New York, 2 issues, [broken series], May 1, 1976-Jan. 8, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Voz Fronteriza, published by the University of California at San Diego, 4 issues, [broken series], Feb. 2, 1976-May 1980 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Wall Street Journal, 2 issues, [broken series], Sept. 13, 1977-Dec. 6, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Washington Post, 1 issue, Aug. 22, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Workers Policy, published by the Cross Union Classwide Caucus in New York City, 1 issue, Aug./Sept. 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - World Magazine, 1 issue, Sept. 1, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Zapata, Comité Nacional de la Central Independiente de Obreros Agrícolas y Campesinos in Mexico, 1 issue, Jun. 1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Oversize Items: El Calendario Chicano 1976;Tape Recording of Corona from SERIES I. (Box 54)